<Builders DateGenerated="2022-04-09T17:13:44"><Corporation><CorporateBuilderNumber>28137</CorporateBuilderNumber><CorporateState>MO</CorporateState><CorporateName>HAWTHORNE CREEK HOMES</CorporateName><Builder><BuilderNumber>28138</BuilderNumber><BrandName>Hawthorne Creek Homes</BrandName><BrandLogo_Med ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/08/Hawthorne-Creek-Homes-Logo-Webl.png</BrandLogo_Med><ReportingName>Hawthorne Creek Homes</ReportingName><DefaultLeadsEmail LeadsPerMessage="All">leads@thebdx.com</DefaultLeadsEmail><BuilderWebsite>hawthornecreekhomes.com</BuilderWebsite><Subdivision Status="Active"><SubdivisionNumber>28138</SubdivisionNumber><SubdivisionName>Hawthorne Creek Homes</SubdivisionName><BuildOnYourLot>0</BuildOnYourLot><SalesOffice><Address OutOfCommunity="0"><Street1>873 E. Ashford Ave</Street1><City>Nixa</City><State>MO</State><ZIP>65714</ZIP></Address></SalesOffice><SubDescription>Hawthorne Creek Homes is owned and operated by Stan and Regina Gutshall, who have over 40 years experience in new home construction from Florida to California. Having built homes in major metropolitan markets, they have brought innovative designs and cutting edge technology to the Southwest Missouri market</SubDescription><SubImage SequencePosition="1" Title="House1" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-Brookstone-FH.jpg</SubImage><SubImage SequencePosition="2" Title="House1" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-Brookstone-EC.jpg</SubImage><SubImage SequencePosition="3" Title="House1" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-Salibury-FH.jpg</SubImage><SubImage SequencePosition="4" Title="House1" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-Salibury-EC.jpg</SubImage><SubWebsite>hawthornecreekhomes.com</SubWebsite><Plan Type="SingleFamily"><PlanNumber>89101699288695807645838737118</PlanNumber><PlanName>Pimlico Floor Plan</PlanName><PlanNotAvailable>0</PlanNotAvailable><PlanTypeName>Single Family</PlanTypeName><BasePrice>0.00</BasePrice><BaseSqft>2789</BaseSqft><Baths>2</Baths><HalfBaths>0</HalfBaths><Bedrooms MasterBedLocation="Down">4</Bedrooms><Garage>4.0</Garage><Description>Welcome to &#8220;The Pimlico.&#8221; This story and a half plan starts at 2789 livable square feet, 3 bedrooms with loft, 2.5 baths, and a 3 car garage (4+ cars and basement available). Your exterior choices of brick, stone, stucco cement board, LP, or vinyl siding feature our latest designs for the &#8220;English Cottage,&#8221; which comes with a front terrace or a &#8220;Farmhouse,&#8221; which includes a covered front porch with composite decking. These new designs mimic the latest market trends of today. This home is perfect for the family with school-age children or for when they come back to visit. As with all of our floor plans they are open, light, and bright, which is accomplished with over-sized windows throughout. Upon entering the foyer, the home opens up to expansive views of the main floor plan. Up front it features a formal dining room or a private in-home office (your choice). The stairs are located at the entry for easy access to the upstairs. The family room is expansive and features a tall fireplace and an optional window seat for out-front viewing and relaxation. The family room also features a vaulted ceiling or tray ceiling (your choice) with a back wall of windows for great views. The &#189; bath is convenient for all downstairs activities. Custom-built cabinetry is featured throughout; the kitchen includes granite countertops and also features a large island (optional designs available) and a separate breakfast nook along with an over-sized walk-in pantry. The master suite with cove lightin</Description><PlanImages><ElevationImage SequencePosition="1" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-Pimlico-FH.jpg</ElevationImage><ElevationImage SequencePosition="2" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-Pimlico-EC.jpg</ElevationImage></PlanImages><PlanWebsite>https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/floor-plans/pimlico/</PlanWebsite></Plan><Plan Type="SingleFamily"><PlanNumber>711026122181967819349594125537</PlanNumber><PlanName>Ashford Floor Plan</PlanName><PlanNotAvailable>0</PlanNotAvailable><PlanTypeName>Single Family</PlanTypeName><BasePrice>0.00</BasePrice><BaseSqft>2515</BaseSqft><Baths>2</Baths><HalfBaths>0</HalfBaths><Bedrooms MasterBedLocation="Down">4</Bedrooms><Garage>4.0</Garage><Description>Welcome to &#8220;The Ashford.&#8221; This single story plan starts at 2515 livable square feet with 2 different exteriors and a 3 car garage (4+ cars available). Your exterior choices of brick, stone, stucco cement board, LP, or vinyl siding feature our latest designs for the &#8220;English Cottage,&#8221; which comes with a front terrace or a &#8220;Farmhouse/Craftsman&#8221; which includes a composite deck and covered front porch. These new designs mimic the latest market trends of today. This home is perfect for those who are looking for a single level home (basement and &#189; story available) which is warm, comfortable, and ideal for entertainment. There are 2 living areas, the family room and the sunroom. The family room features a vaulted ceiling with a &#8220;Shiplap&#8221; accent (optional) and 2 story windows. As with all of our floor plans, they are open, light, and bright, which is accomplished by 9 foot ceilings and over-sized windows throughout. Upon entering the foyer, the home opens up to expansive views of the main floor plan. Up front it features a formal dining room or a private in-home office (your choice). Custom-built cabinetry is featured throughout; the kitchen has an abundance of cabinets which includes granite countertops and also features an optional island (several designs available), along with a walk-in &#8220;Peek-A-Boo&#8221; pantry. The master suite with cove lighting in the master bedroom is positioned so that it creates its own little private retreat. The master bathroom contains an amazing all tile (no </Description><PlanImages><ElevationImage SequencePosition="1" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-Ashford-CR.jpg</ElevationImage><ElevationImage SequencePosition="2" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-Ashford-EC.jpg</ElevationImage></PlanImages><PlanWebsite>https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/floor-plans/ashford/</PlanWebsite></Plan><Plan Type="SingleFamily"><PlanNumber>115348487654090917398413402495</PlanNumber><PlanName>Carrington Floor Plan</PlanName><PlanNotAvailable>0</PlanNotAvailable><PlanTypeName>Single Family</PlanTypeName><BasePrice>0.00</BasePrice><BaseSqft>2681</BaseSqft><Baths>2</Baths><HalfBaths>0</HalfBaths><Bedrooms MasterBedLocation="Down">4</Bedrooms><Garage>4.0</Garage><Description>Welcome to &#8220;The Carrington.&#8221; This plan starts at 2681 livable square feet with 2 different exteriors and a 3 car garage (4+ cars available). Your exterior choices of brick, stone, stucco cement board, LP, or vinyl siding feature our latest designs for the &#8220;English Cottage,&#8221; which comes with a front covered terrace or a &#8220;Craftsman,&#8221; which includes a covered front porch with composite decking. These new designs mimic the latest market trends of today. This home is perfect for those who are looking for a single level home (basements available) which has a &#8220;Wow&#8221; factor yet is comfortable and ideal for entertainment. There are 2 living areas, the family room and the sunroom, which can be separated by a 2-sided fireplace for viewing from both areas. The family room features a tray ceiling up to 11&#8217; high. As with all of our floor plans they are open, light, and bright, which is accomplished by 9 foot ceilings and over-sized windows throughout the rest of the home. Upon entering the foyer, the home opens up to expansive views of the main floor plan. Up front it features a formal dining room or a private in-home office (your choice). Custom-built cabinetry is featured throughout; the kitchen has an abundance of cabinets, including granite countertops and a large island (several designs available).The kitchen also has a separate breakfast nook and a walk-in &#8220;Peek-A-Boo&#8221; pantry. The master suite with cove lighting is positioned such that it creates its own little private retreat. The ma</Description><PlanImages><ElevationImage SequencePosition="1" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-Carrington-CR.jpg</ElevationImage><ElevationImage SequencePosition="2" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-Carrington-EC.jpg</ElevationImage></PlanImages><PlanWebsite>https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/floor-plans/carrington/</PlanWebsite></Plan><Plan Type="SingleFamily"><PlanNumber>852054645140420546143750278596</PlanNumber><PlanName>Oak Knoll Floor Plan</PlanName><PlanNotAvailable>0</PlanNotAvailable><PlanTypeName>Single Family</PlanTypeName><BasePrice>0.00</BasePrice><BaseSqft>3223</BaseSqft><Baths>2</Baths><HalfBaths>0</HalfBaths><Bedrooms MasterBedLocation="Down">4</Bedrooms><Garage>4.0</Garage><Description>Welcome to &#8220;The Oak Knoll.&#8221; This plan is truly unique in that it can be built as a 2405 square foot single level or add a 230 square foot sunroom and/or an upstairs bonus area for an additional 588 sq.ft. of footage with 2 different exteriors and a 3 car garage (4+ cars available). Your exterior choices of brick, stone, stucco cement board, LP, or vinyl siding feature our latest designs for the &#8220;Craftsman or Farm House,&#8221; both of which have a covered front porch with composite decking. These new designs mimic the latest market trends of today. This home is perfect for the buyer looking for versatility in their ever-changing lifestyle (basements available). As with all of our floor plans they are open, light, and bright, which is accomplished by 9 foot ceilings and over-sized windows throughout. Upon entering the foyer, the home opens up to expansive views of the entire main floor plan. Up front it features a formal dining room or a private in-home office (your choice). Custom-built cabinetry is featured throughout; the kitchen includes granite countertops, a large island (several designs available), an octagon &#8220;Breakfast Nook,&#8221; and a walk-in &#8220;Peek-a Boo Pantry&#8221;. Off of the dining room we have an optional &#8220;Butler Pantry&#8221; convenient for entertainment. The master suite with cove lighting is positioned such that it creates its own little private retreat. The master bathroom contains an amazing all tile (no plastics here) walk-in shower, dual vanities with individual medicine cabin</Description><PlanImages><ElevationImage SequencePosition="1" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-OakKnoll-CR.jpg</ElevationImage><ElevationImage SequencePosition="2" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-OakKnoll-FH.jpg</ElevationImage><ElevationImage SequencePosition="3" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-OakKnoll-EC.jpg</ElevationImage></PlanImages><PlanWebsite>https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/floor-plans/oak-knoll/</PlanWebsite></Plan><Plan Type="SingleFamily"><PlanNumber>19137617531033385613189097639</PlanNumber><PlanName>Salisbury Floor Plan</PlanName><PlanNotAvailable>0</PlanNotAvailable><PlanTypeName>Single Family</PlanTypeName><BasePrice>0.00</BasePrice><BaseSqft>2878</BaseSqft><Baths>2</Baths><HalfBaths>0</HalfBaths><Bedrooms MasterBedLocation="Down">4</Bedrooms><Garage>4.0</Garage><Description>Welcome to &#8220;The Salisbury.&#8221; The Salisbury is similar to the Pimlico in that it is a story and a half plan which starts with 1,708 square feet on the 1st floor and up to 1,170 square feet on the 2nd floor for a total of 2,878 livable square feet. The master suite is on the 1st floor and then the secondary bedrooms upstairs with a huge loft. This home features 2.5 baths and a 3 car garage, one being a tandem to accommodate those narrow lots (basement available). Your exterior choices of brick, stone, stucco cement board, LP, or vinyl siding feature our latest designs for the &#8220;English Cottage&#8221; and &#8221;Farmhouse,&#8221; which both come with a front terrace having French doors open to the front living room. These new designs mimic the latest market trends of today. This home is perfect for the family with school-age children and young adults or for when they come back to visit. As with all of our floor plans they are open, light, and bright, which is accomplished by over-sized windows throughout. Upon entering the foyer, the home opens up to expansive views of the main floor plan. It features your living room with a vaulted ceiling, informal dining area, and a private in-home office. The stairs are located at mid-entry for easy access to the upstairs. The &#189; bath is conveniently located behind the kitchen, adjacent to the laundry room, mud room, and the garage. Custom-built cabinetry is featured throughout; the kitchen includes granite countertops and also features a large island (optional </Description><PlanImages><ElevationImage SequencePosition="1" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-Salibury-FH.jpg</ElevationImage><ElevationImage SequencePosition="2" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-Salibury-EC.jpg</ElevationImage></PlanImages><PlanWebsite>https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/floor-plans/salibury/</PlanWebsite></Plan><Plan Type="SingleFamily"><PlanNumber>652474492610830698718799034645</PlanNumber><PlanName>The Abbey Floor Plan</PlanName><PlanNotAvailable>0</PlanNotAvailable><PlanTypeName>Single Family</PlanTypeName><BasePrice>0.00</BasePrice><BaseSqft>2058</BaseSqft><Baths>2</Baths><HalfBaths>0</HalfBaths><Bedrooms MasterBedLocation="Down">4</Bedrooms><Garage>4.0</Garage><Description>Welcome to &#8220;The Abbey.&#8221; This single-story plan starts at 2058 livable square feet with 2 different exteriors, and a 2 &#189; car garage (3+ cars available). Your exterior choices of brick, stone, stucco cement board, LP, or vinyl siding feature our latest designs for the &#8220;English Cottage&#8221; which comes with a front terrace or a &#8220;farmhouse/craftsman&#8221; which includes a composite deck and covered front porch. These new designs mimic the latest market trends of today. This home is perfect for the move-up buyer and those looking to downsize to simplify their lives (basement and &#189; story available). As with all of our floor plans they are open, light, and bright, which is accomplished by 9 foot ceilings and over-sized windows throughout. Upon entering the foyer, the home opens up to expansive views of the main floor plan. Up front it features a formal dining room or a private in home office (your choice). Custom-built cabinetry is featured throughout; the kitchen includes granite countertops and also features a large island with a good traffic pattern, along with a walk-in pantry. The master suite with cove lighting and a 10-foot ceiling is positioned such that it creates a private retreat. The master bathroom contains an amazing all tile (no plastics here) walk-in shower, dual sinks, and access to a large walk-in closet with an alcove for an in-home safe or additional storage. For convenience, the master closet has direct access to the laundry room, which also has its own built-in closet. </Description><PlanImages><ElevationImage SequencePosition="1" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-The-Abbey-FH.jpg</ElevationImage><ElevationImage SequencePosition="2" ReferenceType="URL">https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/wp-content/uploads/2019/09/HCH-The-Abbey-EC.jpg</ElevationImage></PlanImages><PlanWebsite>https://hawthornecreekhomes.com/floor-plans/the-abbey/</PlanWebsite></Plan></Subdivision></Builder></Corporation></Builders>